Front-end Developer Hyunseok Kim

Toronto ON, M6C 4B4, Canada

mobile: 437.350.9079 e-mail: dragmove@gmail.com

github: https://github.com/dragmove

Summary

Versatile Front-end developer with 13+ years of experience, developing interactive websites and applications in various environments. Specialized in Javascript and delicate motion.

Portfolio

https://dragmove-df96f.firebaseapp.com/

Portfolio website based on React, redux, redux-saga, RxJS, styled-component, Node.js Express, webpack, etc.

Open source activities

aid.js

https://www.npmjs.com/package/aid.js

A bundle of Javascript util library to help developers. Most sources were

tested by Jasmine.

Downloaded more than 34,000 on NPM(Feb 2019).

kihon

https://www.npmjs.com/package/kihon

A bundle of lite components which provide straightforward interactive UI.

Support ES2015+.

Downloaded more than 5,000 on NPM(Feb 2019).

Private services

Capture - Webpage Fullscreen Capture

Sep 2016 - current

https://appsto.re/kr/rxiFeb.i

iOS Native App to capture entire webpage on iPhone screen. (Currently working under iOS 13)

Designed App, and developed by Swift language. Support English, Japanese,

Korean, Chinese(Simplified) languages for localization.

Ranked 70th in the 'productivity' category on the App store Korea(24th May 2018).

Downloaded more than 43,200 from the App store(Feb 2019).

Experience

NCSOFT / Senior Front-end developer

Jul 2014 - Aug 2019

Developed responsive community website, simulator applications, internal platform, responsive promotion websites, UI components, and Javascript modules.

Markdown editor on Mink messaging App

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019, Mink messenger development department

// React, redux, redux-saga, immer, webpack, etc.

Developed responsive community website, simulator applications.

Developed Markdown editor based on TUI Editor, and applied to internal messaging application named Mink.

Set up Unit test environment using Jest.

Maintained issues related to Javascript and React components.

Game Pre-order responsive websites

May 2019 - Jun 2019, Mobile game web development team // jQuey, RxJS, ScrollMagic, webpack, etc.

Developed responsive websites with parallax scrolling effect.

Developed various prototype motion for supporting designers.

Collaborated with Back-end developers for OAuth authentication.

Set up development environment using webpack, babel, gulp, plugins, libraries.

Blade&Soul Training simulation App 3.0 / 2.0

Nov 2016 / May 2013 - Nov 2013, Online game web development team // jQuey, lodash, webpack

Developed web application running on in-game web browser for simulating Skill tree of PC game.

Collaborated with Game developers, Back-end developers to apply simulated datas by users between web and game.

NCT Blade&Soul Global Launcher

Jun 2014, Online game web development team // Angular JS 1.1, j Query

Developed web application running on browser in PC Launcher for installing and running PC game with 2 Front-end developers.

Collaborated with PC application developers.

- VW / Interactive Director

Dec 2009 - Aug 2012, Interactive department

Official / Promotion websites

// Flash Actionscript 3.0, Flash Builder 4.x

Developed various Official and Promotion websites (Hyundai E&C, Samsung card, CJ ninebridge, etc) with 1-2 Flash developers.

- VRICKS REPUBLIC / Senior Interactive Designer

Jul 2007 - Sep 2009, Interactive department

Developed various Flash websites and RIA(W-Store, Woongjin coway, LeCoq sportif, Samsung fire, etc) using Flash Actionscript 2.0 / 3.0 with 2-4 Flash developers.

Samsung fire RIA for insurance claim

Oct 2008 - Dec 2008, Interactive department // Flash Actionscript 3.0

Developed Flash RIA for policyholders claiming insurance money. Collaborated with Back-end developers working at Samsung fire.

Mr.Pizza website

Oct 2007 - Dec 2007, Interactive department // Flash Actionscript 2.0

Developed Full Flash website for customers who order pizza online with 2 Flash developers.

- SALTCAKE / Junior Flash Actionscripter

Mar 2006 - Mar 2007

Developed various Flash websites and GUI applications using Flash Actionscript 2.0(LG Electronics, Motorola, Ritzcarlton seoul, etc).

Pantech SKY dialer / SKY IE5 GUI

Jul 2006 - Mar 2007, Design team // Flash Lite 1.1

Developed Flash dialer, GUI on mobile device with Embedded developers working at Pantech. Achieved the first Flash dialer launched from Pantech.

Awards

&Award 2011 Winner

Jan 2012, KDAIA - tourism / leisure

CJ Ninebridge website.

Web Award Korea 2011 Grand Prize

Nov 2011, kipfa - construction

Hyundai E&C website.

Web Award Korea 2011 Grand Prize

Nov 2011, kipfa - leisure / sports

CJ Ninebridge website.

Korea Digital Media Award 2010 Grand Prize

Oct 2011, KDAIA - chemistry

OCI Group website.

Korea Digital Media Award 2010 Grand Prize

Oct 2011, KDAIA - online education

Daekyo Artimom website.

Web Award Korea 2010 Grand Prize

Nov 2010, kipfa - children education

Daekyo Artimom website.

Web Award Korea 2010 Nominee

Nov 2010, kipfa - service

Sports toto website.

Web Award Korea 2008 Excellent Prize

Nov 2008, kipfa - distribution business

Starcity Mall website.

Web Award Korea 2008 Grand Prize

Nov 2008, kipfa - franchise business

Mr.Pizza website.

Web Award Korea 2008 Nominee

Nov 2008, kipfa - distribution business

W-Store website.

Qualifications

JLPT 1st class

Feb 2006, Japan Foundation

1st class in Japanese language proficiency test.

Industrial Engineer Information Processing

Jun 2002, Human Resources Development Service of Korea

National license.

Education

Kyung Hee University

Mar 2000 - Aug 2006, South Korea

Bachelor of Industrial Engineering, College of Techno engineering. Bachelor of Japanese Language, College of Foreign language.